(self.webpackChunk_N_E=self.webpackChunk_N_E||[]).push([[655],{22408:function(e,a,t){Promise.resolve().then(t.bind(t,18561))},18561:function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a),t.d(a,{default:function(){return h}});var n=t(9268),d=t(86006),i=t(56008);let c=[{metadata:{title:"Web3 Developer Learning Trivia Quiz",tokens:"100000",ticker:"ETH",chain:"ETH",allow:["0xe2445a61dE107fc53dbB741f099EFC7bB6cdF49b"],maxEntries:"50",note:"V2VsY29tZSB0byB0aGUgV2ViMyBEZXZlbG9wZXIgTGVhcm5pbmcgVHJpdmlhIFF1aXohIFRoaXMgcXVpeiBhaW1zIHRvIHRlc3QgeW91ciBrbm93bGVkZ2Ugd2hpbGUgcHJvdmlkaW5nIGVkdWNhdGlvbmFsIGluc2lnaHRzIGludG8gdGhlIHdvcmxkIG9mIGJsb2NrY2hhaW4gYW5kIFdlYjMuIExldCdzIGdldCBzdGFydGVkIQ==",style:{background:"color: #04040",text:"color: #f4f4f4"}},entries:[{author:"0xe2445a61dE107fc53dbB741f099EFC7bB6cdF49b",questions:[{id:"550e8400-e29b-41d4-a716-446655440000",answers:["1"]},{id:"6ba7b810-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c8",answers:["3"]},{id:"6ba7b811-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c9",answers:["3"]},{id:"6ba7b812-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c7",answers:["3"]},{id:"6ba7b813-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c6",answers:["3"]}]},{author:"0xe2445a61dE107fc53dbB741f09dwdC7bB6cdF49b",questions:[{id:"550e8400-e29b-41d4-a716-446655440000",answers:["2"]},{id:"6ba7b810-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c8",answers:["1"]},{id:"6ba7b811-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c9",answers:["3"]},{id:"6ba7b812-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c7",answers:["3"]},{id:"6ba7b813-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c6",answers:["3"]}]}],questions:[{id:"550e8400-e29b-41d4-a716-446655440000",question:"What does a blockchain primarily serve as?",note:"QSBibG9ja2NoYWluIGlzIGEgcHVibGljIGxlZGdlciB0aGF0IHJlY29yZHMgdHJhbnNhY3Rpb25zIGFjcm9zcyBtYW55IGNvbXB1dGVycy4gSXQncyByZXNpc3RhbnQgdG8gbW9kaWZpY2F0aW9uLCBlbmhhbmNpbmcgdHJhbnNwYXJlbmN5IGFuZCBzZWN1cml0eS4=",answers:[{caption:"A public ledger"},{caption:"A private database"},{caption:"A chat application"},{caption:"A video streaming service"}]},{id:"6ba7b810-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c8",question:"Which language is primarily used to write Ethereum smart contracts?",note:"U29saWRpdHkgaXMgdGhlIG1haW4gcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2UgZm9yIGRldmVsb3Bpbmcgc21hcnQgY29udHJhY3RzIG9uIHRoZSBFdGhlcmV1bSBibG9ja2NoYWluLiBJdCB3YXMgZGVzaWduZWQgZm9yIGNyZWF0aW5nIGNvbXBsZXggY29udHJhY3RzIGFuZCBkQXBwcy4=",answers:[{caption:"Python"},{caption:"Ruby"},{caption:"Solidity"},{caption:"Swift"}]},{id:"6ba7b811-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c9",question:"What does 'gas' represent in the Ethereum ecosystem?",note:"SW4gRXRoZXJldW0sICdnYXMnIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlIGNvbXB1dGF0aW9uYWwgd29yayByZXF1aXJlZCB0byBleGVjdXRlIG9wZXJhdGlvbnMuIFVzZXJzIHBheSBnYXMgZmVlcyBpbiBFdGhlciB0byBpbmNlbnRpdmUgbWluZXJzIHRvIGluY2x1ZGUgdGhlaXIgdHJhbnNhY3Rpb25zIGluIGEgYmxvY2su",answers:[{caption:"Energy"},{caption:"Code complexity"},{caption:"Transaction fees"},{caption:"Internet speed"}]},{id:"6ba7b812-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c7",question:"What is a DAO?",note:"REFPcyBhcmUgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9ucyByZXByZXNlbnRlZCBieSBzbWFydCBjb250cmFjdHMgb24gdGhlIGJsb2NrY2hhaW4sIHdoaWNoIGFyZSBjb250cm9sbGVkIGJ5IHdyaXR0ZW4gY29kZSBhbmQgY29uc2Vuc3VhbCBhZ3JlZW1lbnRzLCByYXRoZXIgdGhhbiBhIGNlbnRyYWxpemVkIGF1dGhvcml0eS4=",answers:[{caption:"Data Analysis Organization"},{caption:"Decentralized Autonomous Organization"},{caption:"Digital Asset Optimization"},{caption:"Dynamic Address Operation"}]},{id:"6ba7b813-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c6",question:"What is the function of Oracles in blockchain?",note:"T3JhY2xlcyBhcmUgdGhpcmQtcGFydHkgc2VydmljZXMgdGhhdCBmZWVkIHNtYXJ0IGNvbnRyYWN0cyB3aXRoIGV4dGVybmFsIGluZm9ybWF0aW9uLCBlbmFibGluZyB0aGVtIHRvIGV4ZWN1dGUgYmFzZWQgb24gZGF0YSBsaWtlIHByaWNlIGZlZWRzLCB3ZWF0aGVyIGNvbmRpdGlvbnMsIG9yIG90aGVyIHJlYWwtd29ybGQgZXZlbnRzLg==",answers:[{caption:"Predicting the future"},{caption:"Providing external data to smart contracts"},{caption:"Fixing bugs in the code"},{caption:"Optimizing gas costs"}]}]},{metadata:{title:"Web3 Developer Learning Trivia Quiz 2",tokens:"100000",ticker:"ETH",chain:"ETH",allow:["0xe2445a61dE107fc53dbB741f099EFC7bB6cdF49b"],maxEntries:"50",note:"V2VsY29tZSB0byB0aGUgV2ViMyBEZXZlbG9wZXIgTGVhcm5pbmcgVHJpdmlhIFF1aXohIFRoaXMgcXVpeiBhaW1zIHRvIHRlc3QgeW91ciBrbm93bGVkZ2Ugd2hpbGUgcHJvdmlkaW5nIGVkdWNhdGlvbmFsIGluc2lnaHRzIGludG8gdGhlIHdvcmxkIG9mIGJsb2NrY2hhaW4gYW5kIFdlYjMuIExldCdzIGdldCBzdGFydGVkIQ==",style:{background:"color: #04040",text:"color: #f4f4f4"}},entries:[{author:"0xe2445a61dE107fc53dbB741f099EFC7bB6cdF49b",questions:[{id:"550e8400-e29b-41d4-a716-446655440000",answers:["1"]},{id:"6ba7b810-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c8",answers:["3"]}]}],questions:[{id:"550e8400-e29b-41d4-a716-446655440000",question:"What does a blockchain primarily serve as?",note:"QSBibG9ja2NoYWluIGlzIGEgcHVibGljIGxlZGdlciB0aGF0IHJlY29yZHMgdHJhbnNhY3Rpb25zIGFjcm9zcyBtYW55IGNvbXB1dGVycy4gSXQncyByZXNpc3RhbnQgdG8gbW9kaWZpY2F0aW9uLCBlbmhhbmNpbmcgdHJhbnNwYXJlbmN5IGFuZCBzZWN1cml0eS4=",answers:[{caption:"A public ledger"},{caption:"A private database"},{caption:"A chat application"},{caption:"A video streaming service"}]},{id:"6ba7b810-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c8",question:"Which language is primarily used to write Ethereum smart contracts?",note:"U29saWRpdHkgaXMgdGhlIG1haW4gcHJvZ3JhbW1pbmcgbGFuZ3VhZ2UgZm9yIGRldmVsb3Bpbmcgc21hcnQgY29udHJhY3RzIG9uIHRoZSBFdGhlcmV1bSBibG9ja2NoYWluLiBJdCB3YXMgZGVzaWduZWQgZm9yIGNyZWF0aW5nIGNvbXBsZXggY29udHJhY3RzIGFuZCBkQXBwcy4=",answers:[{caption:"Python"},{caption:"Ruby"},{caption:"Solidity"},{caption:"Swift"}]},{id:"6ba7b811-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c9",question:"What does 'gas' represent in the Ethereum ecosystem?",note:"SW4gRXRoZXJldW0sICdnYXMnIHJlcHJlc2VudHMgdGhlIGNvbXB1dGF0aW9uYWwgd29yayByZXF1aXJlZCB0byBleGVjdXRlIG9wZXJhdGlvbnMuIFVzZXJzIHBheSBnYXMgZmVlcyBpbiBFdGhlciB0byBpbmNlbnRpdmUgbWluZXJzIHRvIGluY2x1ZGUgdGhlaXIgdHJhbnNhY3Rpb25zIGluIGEgYmxvY2su",answers:[{caption:"Energy"},{caption:"Code complexity"},{caption:"Transaction fees"},{caption:"Internet speed"}]},{id:"6ba7b812-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c7",question:"What is a DAO?",note:"REFPcyBhcmUgb3JnYW5pemF0aW9ucyByZXByZXNlbnRlZCBieSBzbWFydCBjb250cmFjdHMgb24gdGhlIGJsb2NrY2hhaW4sIHdoaWNoIGFyZSBjb250cm9sbGVkIGJ5IHdyaXR0ZW4gY29kZSBhbmQgY29uc2Vuc3VhbCBhZ3JlZW1lbnRzLCByYXRoZXIgdGhhbiBhIGNlbnRyYWxpemVkIGF1dGhvcml0eS4=",answers:[{caption:"Data Analysis Organization"},{caption:"Decentralized Autonomous Organization"},{caption:"Digital Asset Optimization"},{caption:"Dynamic Address Operation"}]},{id:"6ba7b813-9dad-11d1-80b4-00c04fd430c6",question:"What is the function of Oracles in blockchain?",note:"T3JhY2xlcyBhcmUgdGhpcmQtcGFydHkgc2VydmljZXMgdGhhdCBmZWVkIHNtYXJ0IGNvbnRyYWN0cyB3aXRoIGV4dGVybmFsIGluZm9ybWF0aW9uLCBlbmFibGluZyB0aGVtIHRvIGV4ZWN1dGUgYmFzZWQgb24gZGF0YSBsaWtlIHByaWNlIGZlZWRzLCB3ZWF0aGVyIGNvbmRpdGlvbnMsIG9yIG90aGVyIHJlYWwtd29ybGQgZXZlbnRzLg==",answers:[{caption:"Predicting the future"},{caption:"Providing external data to smart contracts"},{caption:"Fixing bugs in the code"},{caption:"Optimizing gas costs"}]}]}];var s=t(74357),o=t.n(s),l=t(81301),b=t.n(l);let r=b()(()=>Promise.resolve(()=>{let[e,a]=(0,d.useState)(0),[t,s]=(0,d.useState)([""]),[l,b]=(0,d.useState)(!1),r=(0,i.usePathname)();(0,i.useRouter)();let h=r.match(/\/quiz\/(.*?)\/export/),G="";if(h&&h.length>1){let e=h[1];G=decodeURIComponent(e),console.log(e)}else console.log("No match found");let[u,g]=(0,d.useState)(function(){let e={},a=c.find(e=>e.metadata.title===G);a.entries.forEach(a=>{let t=a.author,n=a.questions;e[t]||(e[t]={author:t,questions:[],score:0}),e[t].questions=n});let t=Object.values(e);return t});(0,d.useEffect)(()=>{console.log(u)},[u]);let I=c.find(e=>e.metadata.title===G),m=I.questions,{question:p,answers:B}=m[e],y=e=>{s(Array(e.toString()))},Z=()=>{let e=[];e.push(["Author","Score","Question ID","Given Option"]),u.forEach(a=>{a.questions.forEach(t=>{e.push([a.author,a.score,t.id,t.answers])})});let a=o().unparse(e),t=new Blob([a],{type:"text/csv"}),n=document.createElement("a");n.href=window.URL.createObjectURL(t),n.download="quiz_results.csv",n.click()};return(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[(0,n.jsx)("h1",{children:"Grading of answers"}),(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:"question",children:[(0,n.jsxs)("h2",{children:["Question ",e+1]}),(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:p}),(0,n.jsx)("ul",{children:B.map((e,a)=>(0,n.jsx)("li",{children:(0,n.jsxs)("label",{children:[(0,n.jsx)("input",{type:"radio",name:"answer",value:e.caption,checked:t[0]===a.toString(),onChange:()=>y(a)}),e.caption]})},a))}),(0,n.jsx)("button",{onClick:()=>{let n=[...u];n.forEach(a=>{let d=a.questions[e].answers.includes(t[0].toString());if(console.log(d),d){let e=n.findIndex(e=>e.author===a.author);-1!==e&&(n[e]={...n[e],score:n[e].score+1},console.log(n),g(n),console.log(u))}});let d=e+1;d<m.length?(a(d),s([""])):(b(!0),Z())},children:e===m.length-1?"Finish Grading":"Next Question"})]}),l&&(0,n.jsx)("p",{children:"Exporting to CSV file"})]})}),{ssr:!1});var h=r}},function(e){e.O(0,[488,667,152,744],function(){return e(e.s=22408)}),_N_E=e.O()}]);